A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, New York Office, Series 22 FA365
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appointments Office, 1959-1965; 1; 9 Cubic Feet
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 23-29, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    October 23 1. New York City - Commodore Hotel 2. Brooklyn - Zion Baptist Church 3. Cornerstone Baptist Church 4. Nazarene Congregational Church 5. Washington Temple, Church of God in Christ 6. 20th Street - Nixon-Lodge rally 7. 11th Street - Lindsay rally October 24 1. New York City - League of Women Voters 2. New York City - Walking tour 3. Plattsburgh - Northway dedication 4. Plattsburgh - Rally October 25 - New York City 1. Five rallies held around city October 26 - New York City 1. Eight rallies held around city 2. Richmond County - Republican Committee Dinner 3. Barry Gray Show - WMCA-Radio October 27 - Suffolk County 1. Rallies held in Patchogue, Port Jefferson, Stony Brook, Smithtown, Commack, Huntingdon, and Lindenhurst 2. Huntingdon Town Republican Headquarters, dinner October 28 - Nassau County 1. Luncheon at Garden City Hotel with Citizens for Nixon-Lodge 2. Rallies held in Long Beach, Massapequa Park, Rockville Center, Levittown, Franklin Square October 29 - New York City 1. Three Walking Tours around city 2. Luncheon at 369th Regiment Armory 3. Seven rallies held around city
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 31-November 7, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    October 31 - New York City 1. New York University, rally 2. Walking tour 3. Taping of "Today" show November 2 1. Motorcade with President Eisenhower, Vice President Nixon, and Ambassador Lodge 2. New York Coliseum with same November 3 - New York City 1. Three rallies held around city 2. Dedication of Loral Electronics plant 3. Speech to Harvard Business School November 4 - New York City 1. Four rallies held around city 2. Two block parties November 5 - Queens 1. Flushing 2. Shopping Centers 3. Rally at Manhattan College
  - New York, New York, November 14, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    1. Waldorf-Astoria Hotel - reception 2. American Friends of the Hebrew University
  - West Point, New York; New York, New York, November 30, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    West Point 1. 12th Annual Student Conference on United States Affairs 2. West Point Army Mess New York City 3. United Nations Reception
  - New York, New York, December 2, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    1. Biltmore Hotel - Sigma Delta Chi Annual Convention
  - Kiamesha Lake; New York, New York, December 7, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    1. Kiamisha Lake - Concord Hotel - Association of General Contractors of America 2. New York City - Riverside Church - Corporate Meeting
  - New York, New York, December 8, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    1. Manhattan Center - Committee of International Brotherhood of Electric Workers
  - New York, New York, December 10, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    1. Statler Hilton Hotel - National United Jewish Appeal Conference Dinner Meeting
  - Queens, New York, December 17, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    1. Rochdale Village - United Housing Foundation
  - New York, New York, December 19, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    1. Madison Square Garden - Chanukah Festival for Israel
  - New York, New York, December 22, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    1. Gotham Hotel - Westchester Leaders and Legislators
  - New York State, December 27-29, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    1. White Plains - Opening of Cross-Westchester Expressway 2. New York City - Birthday Dinner for Edward Corsi, LaGuardia House
  - Events at the Executive Mansion, Albany, New York (Box 2, Folder 38)
    1. Memo dated 12/21/60 describing January 1961, events at the Governor's Mansion in Albany.
  - Albany, New York, January 3, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    1. Opening of Central Office, Bureau of Motor Vehicles
  - Syracuse, New York, January 4, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    1. Syracuse Press Club, dinner and reception
  - Albany, New York, January 9, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    1. New York State Builders Association, Inc.
  - Albany, New York, January 10, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    1. New York State Women's Legislative Forum
  - Chicago, Illinois, January 11, 1961; Los Angeles, California, January 12, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    Chicago, Illinois 1. Opening of New York State Department of Commerce, Chicago Office Los Angeles, California 1. Opening of New York State Department of Commerce, Los Angeles Office
  - Albany, New York, January 16, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    1. New York State Citizen's Council on Traffic Safety
  - Albany, New York, January 18, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    1. New York State Agricultural Society Annual Farm Dinner
  - Plainview, New York; New York, New York, January 19, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    1. Plainview - Opening of The Harmon-Kardon Plant 2. New York City - building Trades Employers Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel
  - Washington, DC, January 20-21, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    January 20 - Inauguration of President-elect Kennedy 1. U.S. Capitol 2. Luncheon following January 21 1. Alfalfa Club Dinner, guest of Senator Keating
  - Albany, New York, January 24, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    1. New York State Association of Agricultural Fair Societies
  - Albany, New York; New York, New York, January 26, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Albany, New York 1. New York State County Highway Superintendents Association - 50th Anniversary Meeting New York City 1. Congregation Emanu-el Men's Club 2. Westchester Republican County Committee
  - New York, New York, January 27, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    1. Society of Foreign Counsels reception
  - Troy, New York, January 30, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    1. Retirement Dinner for Superintendent Francis S. McGarvey
  - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, February 1, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    1. Governors and Mayors Meeting with Delaware River Basin Authority
  - New York, New York, February 4, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    1. National Federation of Young Republicans 2. American Institute of Banking
  - Albany, New York; Buffalo, New York; Albany, New York, February 6, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Albany 1. New York State Council of Churches Buffalo 1. The Association of Towns Meeting Albany 1. Empire State Chamber of Commerce, Annual Legislative Dinner
  - Niagara, New York, February 9, 1961; Lake Placid, New York, February 10, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Niagara 1. Niagara Falls Chamber of Commerce Dinner 2. Niagara University Ceremony 3. Lunch - Niagara University Cafeteria 4. Observation Tower, State Park Commission Lake Placid 1. Banquet, St. Moritz Hotel 2. Olympic Arena
  - New York, New York, February 12, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    1. Brooklyn-Kings County Republican Organization Annual Lincoln Day Dinner, Hotel St. George 2. New York County Republican Committee Annual Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria
  - Albany, New York, February 13, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    1. Business and Professional Women's Clubs of New York State, Inc., Legislative Conference
  - Albany, New York, February 14, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    1. Butch McMorran's cocktail party, University Club 2. Legislative Dinner of Veterans of Foreign Wars, Ten Eyck Hotel 3. Reception, Executive Mansion 4. Annual dance of Republican Women of Legislature, Ten Eyck Hotel 5. Return to Mansion
  - Albany, New York, February 20, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    1. American Meat Institute 2. New York State Publishers Association
  - Albany, New York, February 21, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    1. Legislative Dinner, American Legion
  - Albany, New York, February 22, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    1. Westchester County members and former members of New York State Legislature
  - New York, New York, February 25, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    1. Testimonial Dinner for Bernard Newman given by Federal Club
  - Albany, New York, February 27, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    1. League of Women Voters Annual Legislative Conference
  - Albany, New York, February 28, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    1. New York Farm Bureau
  - Regrets, February, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    1. Kings County American Legion 2. Syracuse University students 3. Council of Social Agencies of Rochester
  - New York, New York, March 1, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    1. Testimonial Dinner for Stanley M. Isaacs
  - Albany, New York, March 2, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    1. Civil Service Employees Association Dinner
  - New York, New York, March 4, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    1. The Inner Circle Dinner
  - Albany, New York, March 7, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    1. Association of Broadcasters Legislative Dinner
  - Albany, New York, March 7, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    1. Nassau County Legislative Dinner
  - New York, New York, March 10, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    1. The Inner Circle Dinner and Show
  - Albany, New York, March 11, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    1. Legislative Correspondents Association Dinner
  - Albany, New York, March 14, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    1. Army National Guard Reception
  - New York, New York, March 15, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    1. United Jewish Appeal Inaugural Dinner
  - New York, New York, March 17, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    1. St. Patrick's Day Parade (reviewing stand)
  - Regrets, March, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    1. Maritime Trades Department 2. County Officers Association 3. Industrial Management Club Conference
  - Rensselaer, New York, April 6, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    1. Sterling-Winthrop Research Institute
  - Kiamesha Lake, New York, April 10, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    1. New York State Federation of Women's Clubs
  - Huntingdon, New York, April 13, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    1. Suffolk County Republican Committee Annual Spring Dinner
  - Elmira, New York, April 14, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    1. New York State Grange - Middle Atlantic Lecturers' Conference
  - Buffalo, New York, April 20, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    1. New York Fraternal Congress Annual Meeting 2. Dedication of New York Nuclear Research Center, University of Buffalo
  - New York, New York, April 23, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    1. Associated Press Reception 2. Urban League Dinner for Louis J. Lefkowitz
  - Yorktown, New York, April 25, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    1. IBM Research Center, dedication
  - New York, New York, April 26, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    1. United Press Reception
  - Albany, New York, April 27, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    1. Law Day Observance, Court of Appeals
  - Jamaica, New York; New York, New York, April 29, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    Jamaica, New York 1. United Housing Federation, dedication of Rochdale Village New York City 1. Parade with Veterans of Foreign Wars
  - Regrets, April, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    1. Harrison Lions Club Dinner 2. Scintilla Management Club 3. St. Johns University 4. Israel Independence Day Reception 5. Philadelphia Fellowship Commission 6. Citizenship Clearing House Conference (event canceled) 7. Greater Utica Citizen's Committee
  - Sterling Forest, New York, May 1, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    1. Press Conference 2. Advisory Council for the Advancement of Industrial Research and Development Symposium
  - New York, New York, May 2, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    1. Citizens Union Searchlight Dinner
  - New York, New York, May 3, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    1. United States World Trade Fair
  - New York, New York, May 16, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    1. Museum of Primitive Art Reception
  - Ravena, New York, May 19, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    1. Atlantic Cement Co., ground breaking
  - Garrison, New York, May 21, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    1. Boscobel Restoration
  - New York, New York; Kiamesha Lake, New York, May 23, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    New York City 1. 50th Anniversary of New York Public Library Kiamesha Lake 1. Annual Convention of the Police Conference
  - Washington, DC, May 24, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    1. Congressional Dinner
  - New York, New York, May 25, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    1. Commerce and Industry Association of New York
  - Glens Falls, New York; Plattsburgh, New York, May 26, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    Glens Falls 1. Glens Falls bypass for Route 87 (Northway) Plattsburgh 1. Hortense B. Sterns Apartments, dedication
  - Tarrytown, New York, May 30, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    1. Memorial Day Observance, Sleepy Hollow Cemetery
  - Regrets, May, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    1. Banquet for Senator Earl W. Brydges 2. National Committee for Children and Youth 3. Joint Meeting of National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) and New York State Elks 4. Dedication of State University College of Education Library in Plattsburgh 5. Minnesota Republicans 6. Police Benevolent Association 7. Beacon Young Republicans 8. Police and fire Fighters Installation Dinner 9. New Jersey Federation of Republican Women
  - New York, New York, June 1, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    1. The Cloisters 2. Yonkers Republican City Committee Dinner/Dance 3. Bronx County Republican Committee Dinner
  - New York, New York, June 3, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    1. Annual Puerto Rican Dinner, Hotel Commodore
  - New York, New York, June 4, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    1. Yeshiva of Flatbush, dedication 2. Puerto Rican Parade 3. Jewish Theological Seminary of America Dinner, Hotel Astor
  - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, June 5, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    1. Kenny's Suburban House - press conference 2. Latin Casino - reception and dinner
  - Syracuse, New York, June 6-7, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    June 6 1. Briefing by Metropolitan Development Commission 2. Interview with Editor of Syracuse "Herald Journal" 3. Luncheon, University Club of Syracuse 4. State Office Building Meetings 5. WSYR Building, meeting with station president 6. Solvay Victory Dinner, Raphael's Restaurant June 7 1. Syracuse "Post Standard" Offices 2. Tour of Industrial Urban Renewal Site 3. WHEN Building, meeting with radio station president 4. Syracuse University Luncheon 5. Tour of Syracuse University Hospital 6. Tour of Upstate College of Medicine 7. Tour of Urban Renewal Area 8. Hotel Syracuse, meetings 9. Private Dinner with Senator John Hughes 10. Onondaga County War Memorial, meeting of Onondaga County Republican Committee 11. Town Meeting, Lincoln Auditorium
  - New York, New York, June 8, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    1. Traffic Safety Poster Award 2. Republican State Committee Luncheon 3. 13th Annual Republican State Committee Dinner
  - New York, New York, June 11, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    1. Dedication of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Wing to the Workmen's Circle Home
  - Albany, New York; Brooklyn, New York; Spring Valley, New York, June 12, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    Albany 1. State University College of Education, Local Government Workshop Luncheon Brooklyn 1. Young Mens' Christian Association (YMCA) meeting with Commissioner George Fowler Spring Valley 1. Rockland County Dinner
  - Garden City, New York, June 13, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    1. Dinner with Nassau County Executive Committee 2. Meeting of Nassau County Republican Club
  - New York, New York, June 14, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    1. National Association of Attorneys General
  - Peekskill, New York; New York City, June 15, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    Peekskill 1. Low cost housing dedication New York City 1. Call on Italian Prime Minister 2. Iona College Alumni Banquet 3. Waldorf Hotel dinner for Italian Prime Minister
  - Albany, New York, June 16, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    1. Visit by Martin Luther King, Jr.
  - Bronx, New York; Albany, New York; Lake Placid, New York, June 20, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    Bronx 1. Tour of new Police Athletic League (PAL) Center Albany 1. State Department Health Building Lake Placid 1. Annual Dinner of the New York State Society of Certified Accountants
  - New York, New York, June 22, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    1. Meeting with Puerto Rican group
  - Nassau County, New York, June 29, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    1. Long Beach Republican Scholarship Fund Dinner
  - Regrets, June, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    1. Fund Raising Dinner, Delaware Township 2. Dairymen's Barbecue 3. Bowling Proprietors' Association of America 4. Greater Utica Citizen's Association 5. Testimonial Tea for Mrs. Rita Develin 6. Annual Dinner, Hawaii Chapter, American Red Cross 7. Luncheon with Governor Brown 8. Jewish War Veterans of New York 9. Commencement, Carson-Newman College 10. Syracuse University 11. Police Athletic League 12. Republican Dance, Tompkinsville
  - New York, New York, July 11, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    1. Reception honoring Russ Clark
  - Binghamton, New York, July 12-14, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    July 12 1. Briefing, Broome Tech Community College 2. WBNF Taping at Sheraton Hotel July 13 1. Harpur College, breakfast 2. Offices of "Evening Press," meeting with the editor 3. Observation point (top of Press Building) 4. Tour of Urban Renewal Area 5. Motor Vehicles and Tax Department Offices 6. Tour of Sheltered Workshop Rehabilitation Center 7. Tour of Binghamton State Hospital 8. Luncheon, Binghamton State Hospital 9. Terminal Point, Penn-Can Highway 10. State Hospital Property 11. Tour of Police Athletic League camp 12. Press Conference 13. Private Dinner 14. Town Meeting, Harpur College Auditorium 15. WINR-TV, live appearance July 14 1. Tour of Saratoga Terrace Housing Project 2. Office of "Sun Bulletin", interview 3. Tour of General Electric Plant 4. Tour of Route 17 (George F. Johnson Highway) 5. Tour of Cadre Plant 6. McKinley Avenue Bridge Site 7. Tour of Endicott Municipal Buildings 8. Endicott-Johnson Administration Building 9. IBM Administration Office 10. Luncheon, Frederick Hotel
  - Albany, New York, July 27, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    1. Annual American Legion Convention 2. American Legion Auxiliary Convention 3. Rensselaer Forestry Camp, ground breaking
  - Regrets, July, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    1. Lake County Republican Committee Rally 2. Fort Plain Restoration Project 3. Allegheny County Young Republican Club
  - Chicago, Illinois, August 14, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    1. National Association of County Officials
  - New York, New York, August 20, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    1. Yankee Stadium, All Negro Championship Ball Game sponsored by International Brotherhood of the Protective Order of Elks (Elks Club) (IBPOE)
  - New York, New York, August 21, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    1. Improved Benevolent of the Protective Order of Elks
  - Rochester, New York, August 22, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    1. Annual Convention of Firemen's Association of the State of New York 2. Monroe County Fair
  - Jones Beach, New York, August 23, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    1. Garden City - Opening of Nassau Republican Headquarters 2. Jones Beach - Governor's Day Ceremonies
  - Utica, New York, August 25, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    1. Italian-American War Veterans of the U.S.
  - Seattle, Washington, August 27-28, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    August 27 1. Reception, Olympic Hotel August 28 1. American Municipal Association Reception 2. Private Appointments and Dinner
  - Regrets, August 1961 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    1. Utica College Campus 2. Fort Schuyler Club 3. Richfield Springs, New York Centennial 4. Essex County Republican Committee 5. Rotary Club of Utica
  - New York, New York, September 2, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    1. Zionist Organization of America
  - New York, New York, September 4, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    1. Labor Day Parade
  - Syracuse, New York, September 5-6, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    September 5 1. Syracuse Chamber of Commerce, reception and dinner September 6 1. "SPICE" (poultry association) Breakfast in Women's Building 2. Tour of Exhibit Buildings 3. Luncheon
  - Brooklyn, New York, September 9, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    1. Young Republican Clubs of Brooklyn 2. Carver Federal Savings and Loan Grand Opening
  - Brooklyn, New York, September 10, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    1. Puerto Rican Parade
  - Upstate New York, September 12-14, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    September 12 1. Ithaca - Dedication of Frank B. Morrison Hall, Department of Animal Husbandry, Cornell University 2. Rochester - Briefing Session 3. Rochester - Dinner and reception 4. Rochester - Republican County Committee Meeting September 13 - Rochester 1. Breakfast with local educators 2. Urban Renewal Housing Project ground breaking ceremonies (3) 3. State Commission Against Discrimination 4. Women's Federation Annual Conference 5. Tours a. Arterial work near post office b. Eastern Expressway c. Xerox Corporation d. Port of Rochester 6. Press Conference 7. Temple B'rith Kodesh buffet supper, speech 8. Town meeting - Rochester Institute of Technology, Ritter Clark Building September 14 - Rochester 1. Breakfast with labor officials 2. Rochester Public Market 3. Rochester Day Care Center for Handicapped Children 4. Eastman Kodak 5. Front Street Urban Renewal Project 6. Midtown Plaza Project 7. Rochester Ad Club 8. Thruway Information Center
  - New York, New York, September 18, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    1. Lincoln Center
  - Watertown, New York, September 20, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    1. Luncheon with local leaders 2. Carthage - Rally 3. Jefferson County Republican Committee, reception and dinner 4. WCNY-TV, one-half hour panel discussion program
  - New York, New York, September 21, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    1. New York Young Republican Club
  - Lake Placid, New York, September 22-23, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    September 22 1. Whiteface Inn cocktail party given by Associated Industries of New York State 2. Dinner, speech September 23 1. Tupper Lake County Club, breakfast
  - New York, New York, September 23, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    1. Union Label and Service Trades Council Dinner
  - Upstate New York, September 25, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    1. Oneonta - Oneonta College of Education, dedication 2. Oneonta - Oneonta College of Education, reception 3. Cooperstown - New York State Publishers Association
  - Upstate New York, September 26-29, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    September 26 1. Arrive Niagara Falls September 27 1. Niagara Falls - Breakfast with local leaders 2. Lockport - Niagara County Courthouse Planning Presentation 3. Lockport - Luncheon Junior Chamber of Commerce 4. Niagara Falls - New York State Council of Carpenters Convention 5. Tour of Niagara County Projects 6. Buffalo - Erie County Economic Advisory Committee, dinner September 28 - Buffalo 1. Breakfast with labor leaders 2. New Conference 3. Tour of Regional Planning and Development Projects 4. National Convention of American Association of Textile Chemists and Colorists 5. Ellicott Mall Housing and Urban Renewal Project 6. State University College of Education at Buffalo 7. Town Meeting, Kleinhans Auditorium September 29 1. Buffalo - Breakfast with local educators 2. Batavia - New York State School for the Blind, dedication of Knight Hall
  - New York, New York, September 29, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    1. National Business League Annual Banquet
  - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 30, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    1. New York State Home Builders Association
  - Regrets, September 1961 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    1. Greenwich Village Chamber of Commerce 2. Genesee County Young Republican Club 3. Watertown Artist Guild 4. Town of Niagara Republican Club 5. Women's Republican Club of Ontario 6. Jericho Republican Club 7. Ischua Creek Watershed Project 8. New Hartford Republican Club 9. Rockville Centre Barbecue 10. Erie County Republican Picnic 11. Midwest Regional Conference of National Federation of Republican Women 12. Labor Day, Phoenix, Arizona 13. Essex County Republican Committee 14. Onondaga County Women's Republican Club 15. National Hardwood Lumber Association 16. 300th Anniversary Celebration, Mamaroneck 17. Empire State Petroleum Association 18. Le Chambre de Commerce de Montreal 19. Canal Museum, Syracuse 20. Gerry Homes, Fredonia
  - New York, New York; Syracuse, New York, October 1, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 144)